Curriculum Vitae

Ali Ayed Hameedi

PERSONAL INFORMATION



Career Objective:

Ali Ayed Hameedi

Al-Qadisiyah, Iraq

**** +964 780 044 0660

theseaali@yahoo.com / aliayedzpec@gmail.com

Sex M | Date of birth 01/01/1990 | Nationality Iraqi

Marital Status; Married Children; 1

I am looking forward to become a member in a leading conglomerate, where my skills will be enhanced and developed. I'm ready to work anywhere to prove myself to deliver better results. I strive to achieve my objectives and work to my full capabilities and expertise. I never undertake my work half-heartedly as I do my work with Pride and full commitment.

PREFERRED JOB

Administrator - Public Relations Officer, HR Officer

Work Experience (6 Years)

HR Officer

Samsung Engineering Company Limited.



Company Industry: Oil/Gas
August 2016 – September 2018
http://www.samsungengineering.co.kr/

I worked as a PRO (Public Relations Officer) and HR (Human Resources) with Samsung

Engineering Company Limited. I'm knowledgeable about Iraqi labor law & Social security law.

Job Profile

- ➤ Planned and control of recruitment process from start to finish using the company recruitment grid system. (receiving request, reviewing job description, posting and sourcing, interviewing, making offer).
- Organized training for staff.
- Updated employee files to document personnel actions and to provide information for payroll and other uses.
- Social Security arrangement and Processing.
- Work permit for expats arrangement and Processing.
- Maintaining all HR paperwork to ensure compliance with relevant legislation.
- Resolving typical and common hiring problems.
- Innovation and Payroll.





PRO Associate

Samsung Engineering Company Limited.

Location: Badra Oil Field, Wasit, Iraq

Company Industry: Oil/Gas June 2014 – March 2016

http://www.samsungengineering.co.kr/

I Worked as a PRO Associate (Public Relations Officer\Access Permit Coordinator) with Samsung Engineering Company Limited.

Job Profile

- ➤ Coordinate with MdOC, Oil Police, Border Police, ISCO and Oil Intelligence for the work process and security issues.
- Responsible for the Access Permit clearance process for Local, Expat Clients and vehicles.
- Arrange for the blood test and VISA process with its documentation.
- > Supervising and supporting SECL subcontractor and other projects teams.
- Administrating, monitoring, providing assistance problem resolution over 2000 employees and troubleshooting the employees' affair.
- Negotiating and liaise with third parties to achieve the companies goals in every time.

ZPEC

Admin and Security Coordinator

Location: Badra, Wasit, Iraq Company Industry: Oil/Drilling January 2014 – June 2014 http://www.zpec.com/en/

Job Profile

I Worked as an Administrator and Security Coordinator with Zhongman Petroleum and

- **Natural Gaz Group**. Acting as company representative for security issues.
 - Responsible for the Security Clearance for the expat staff, local staff and vehicles.
 - Providing assistance, support and problem resolution over for 300 employees.
 - > Arranging the documentation for Visa Cable, Residence Visa and Blood Test.
 - Assisting the HR.

Triple Canopy

Admin and Security Coordinator

Location: Badra, Wasit, Iraq Type of Industry: Security May 2013 – January 2014

http://www.triplecanopy.com/services/

Job Profile







Curriculum Vitae

I worked as an **Administrator and Security Coordinator** with **Triple Canopy Company** for security services and my responsibilities were.

- Recruiting new employees.
- Making the Access Permit and documenting the MRF in Baghdad and Kut.

Education

Bachelor's degree (Bachelor of Art in English language) Grade; good 70.48%

Location: Al-Qadisiya, Iraq **Completion Date:** May 2013

Graduation Project: (Speech Act of Thanking) with very good grade 81%

Skills

Administrator

Level: Expert | Experience: 6 years | Last Used: 6 month or less.

Computer Skills

Level: Expert | Experience: 6 years | Last Used: until now (continued).

Training \ Education

Level: Expert | Experience: 3 years | Last Used: until now (continued).

HR

Level: Officer | Experience 2 years | Last Used: 6 month or less.

Languages

English

Level: Expert | Experience: 11 years or less | Last Used: until now (continued).

Arabic

Native language

References, Certifications and other documents available upon request.

DECLARATION

I hereby declare that the above-furnished information is true to the best of my knowledge and belief.

Ali Ayed Hameedi